Day after day,
يوما بعد يوم،
what's the use of drinking these herbal medicines?
ما فائدة شرب هذه الأدوية العشبية؟
That unfilial son will be the death of me sooner or later.
هذا الابن العقيم سيكون سبب موتي عاجلا أم آجلا.
Master, please calm down.
سيدي، من فضلك اهدأ.
Everything was fine,
كل شيء كان جيدا
but that wretched boy ruined the wedding banquet.
لكن ذلك الصبي البائس أفسد وليمة الزفاف.
How am I going to explain this to the Commander?
كيف سأشرح هذا للقائد؟
The Commander's family has returned all our betrothal gifts.
لقد أعادت عائلة القائد جميع هدايا الخطوبة لنا.
Commander Xu and Miss Xu are just angry for now.
القائد شو والسيدة شو غاضبان الآن فقط.
I'm sure they'll come around once they've calmed down.
أنا متأكد من أنهم سوف يأتون عندما يهدأون.
No.
لا.
I can't let that wretched boy roam freely anymore.
لا أستطيع أن أسمح لهذا الصبي البائس بالتجول بحرية بعد الآن.
I must lock him up
يجب أن أحبسه
and keep him under strict supervision.
وإبقائه تحت رقابة صارمة.
Father, please reconsider.
يا أبي، من فضلك أعد النظر.
If this gets out, it will look bad for us.
إذا انتشر هذا الأمر، فسيكون الأمر سيئًا بالنسبة لنا.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
If it weren't for...
لو لم يكن ل...
Because I feel guilty toward his mother...
لأنني أشعر بالذنب تجاه والدته...
I would
أود
absolutely not tolerate this unfilial son.
لا أتسامح مطلقًا مع هذا الابن العقيم.
Father, don't worry about Miss Xu.
أبي، لا تقلق بشأن الآنسة شو.
I'll take care of it.
سأعتني بالأمر.
Miss Xu has a good impression of me.
لدى السيدة شو انطباع جيد عني.
I believe the relationship between our families will improve soon.
أعتقد أن العلاقة بين عائلاتنا سوف تتحسن قريبا.
Sinan.
سنان.
Do you hate your brother?
هل تكره أخاك؟
He is my own brother after all.
إنه أخي بعد كل شيء.
How could I possibly hold a grudge against him?
كيف يمكنني أن أحمل ضغينة ضده؟
After I marry Miss Xu,
بعد أن تزوجت الآنسة شو،
I will definitely expand the Liu family business
سأقوم بالتأكيد بتوسيع أعمال عائلة ليو
and take good care of him then.
واعتني به جيدا إذن.
Sinan.
سنان.
You are so generous.
أنت كريم جداً.
I indeed chose the right person.
لقد اخترت الشخص المناسب بالفعل.
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
You want to investigate what happened to your parents at Fulu Restaurant.
تريد التحقيق في ما حدث لوالديك في مطعم فولو.
Because...
لأن...
It's been so many years
لقد مرت سنوات عديدة
Could there still be any clues?
هل لا يزال هناك أي أدلة؟
I want to give it a try.
أريد أن أجربه.
Liu Silin's jade pendant
قلادة اليشم من تصميم ليو سيلين
was also lost at Fulu Restaurant back then.
وقد فقدت أيضًا في مطعم فولو في ذلك الوقت.
I feel there's more to this story.
أشعر أن هناك المزيد في هذه القصة.
This Fulu Restaurant...
هذا مطعم فولو...
Although it belongs to the Liu family
على الرغم من أنها تنتمي إلى عائلة ليو
but...
لكن...
The young master's madness
جنون السيد الشاب
is now known throughout the city.
ومن المعروف الآن في جميع أنحاء المدينة.
Besides, a few days ago
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، قبل بضعة أيام
you just ruined the wedding between the Liu family and the Commander's mansion.
لقد دمرت للتو حفل الزفاف بين عائلة ليو وقصر القائد.
It won't be easy for you to get in now.
لن يكون من السهل عليك الدخول الآن.
So I want you to come with me.
لذلك أريدك أن تأتي معي.
Me?
أنا؟
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Fulu Restaurant isn't a place just anyone can enter.
مطعم فولو ليس مكانًا يمكن لأي شخص دخوله.
You two can go to the small restaurant next door.
يمكنكم الذهاب إلى المطعم الصغير المجاور.
Are you hiring?
هل انت توظف؟
You two?
انتما الاثنان؟
We're siblings who fled from famine
نحن أشقاء هربنا من المجاعة
looking for work to feed ourselves.
نبحث عن عمل لإطعام أنفسنا.
We can work for less pay.
يمكننا العمل بأجر أقل.
Manager.
مدير.
These two fled from famine
هذان الاثنان هربا من المجاعة
and want to work at our restaurant.
وأريد العمل في مطعمنا.
All right. I happen to need two helpers.
حسناً، أحتاج إلى مساعدين.
You can stay for now.
يمكنك البقاء الآن.
Thank you, Manager.
شكرا لك يا مدير.
This isn't clean enough.
هذا ليس نظيفا بما فيه الكفاية.
And this too.
وهذا أيضا.
I've been here less than a year.
لقد كنت هنا منذ أقل من عام.
You're asking about something from seven years ago.
أنت تسأل عن شيء حدث قبل سبع سنوات.
How would I know?
كيف سأعرف؟
No idea.
ليس لدي فكرة.
Ma'am.
سيدتي.
How long have you been working here?
منذ متى تعمل هنا؟
At least twenty years.
عشرين سنة على الأقل.
Even the manager hasn't been here as long as I have.
حتى المدير لم يكن هنا لفترة طويلة مثلي.
Then I'd like to ask you something.
إذن أود أن أسألك شيئا.
Do you remember five years ago
هل تتذكر قبل خمس سنوات؟
when the young master held his birthday banquet here?
عندما أقام السيد الشاب حفل عيد ميلاده هنا؟
Isn't the young master insane?
أليس السيد الشاب مجنونًا؟
Why would he hold any banquet?
لماذا يقيم أي وليمة؟
I don't remember. I don't remember.
لا أتذكر. لا أتذكر.
If you two keep slacking off, I won't be so nice anymore!
إذا استمريتما في التراخي، فلن أكون لطيفًا بعد الآن!
And these too.
وهؤلاء أيضا.
You've been leaving early and coming back late
لقد كنت تغادر مبكرًا وتعود متأخرًا
these days. What have you been up to?
هذه الأيام. ماذا كنت تفعل؟
Oh please,
أوه من فضلك
mind your own business.
اهتم بأمورك الخاصة.
The young master is here. Hurry up with those desserts,
السيد الشاب هنا. أسرعوا بتناول الحلويات.
or we'll all be packing our bags and leaving.
أو سنقوم جميعًا بحزم حقائبنا والمغادرة.
Yes, our restaurant used to be so quiet.
نعم، كان مطعمنا هادئًا جدًا.
Thanks to the young master, we now have all these distinguished guests.
بفضل السيد الشاب، أصبح لدينا الآن كل هؤلاء الضيوف المميزين.
Stop the chatter.
أوقف الثرثرة.
Hurry and take these dishes to the young master in the Cuiyu private room.
سارع وخذ هذه الأطباق إلى السيد الشاب في غرفة كوييو الخاصة.
Yes, alright, let's go.
نعم، حسنًا، دعنا نذهب.
Here, Young Master, a toast to you.
تفضل يا سيدي الشاب، نخب لك.
Come on.
تعال.
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
what is Liu Sinan doing here?
ماذا يفعل ليو سينان هنا؟
Now, I am Commander Xu's future son-in-law.
الآن، أنا صهر القائد شو المستقبلي.
And who are those people?
ومن هم هؤلاء الناس؟
In Yuncheng,
في يونتشنغ،
who wouldn't show me some respect?
من لا يظهر لي بعض الاحترام؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
In the future,
في المستقبل،
if you need anything from me,
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء مني،
just say the word.
فقط قل الكلمة.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Cheers.
هتافات.
Drink up.
اشرب.
The Liu Sinan now
ليو سينان الآن
is not the Brother Sinan I used to know.
ليس هو الأخ سنان الذي أعرفه.
I hate those who climb the social ladder through connections.
أنا أكره هؤلاء الذين يصعدون السلم الاجتماعي عن طريق العلاقات.
In the future, I will rely on my own efforts
في المستقبل سأعتمد على جهودي الخاصة
to build my career.
لبناء مسيرتي المهنية.
Anyway, it has nothing to do with me anymore.
على أية حال، لم يعد الأمر له علاقة بي بعد الآن.
Let me see what they're talking about.
دعني أرى ما يتحدثون عنه.
Young Master, here's to you.
سيدي الشاب، هنا لك.
Sinan,
سنان،
there's something I want to discuss with you.
هناك شيء أريد مناقشته معك.
Recently, there's a shipment of opium coming to Yuncheng.
في الآونة الأخيرة، هناك شحنة من الأفيون قادمة إلى يونتشنغ.
I can't hear clearly what they're saying.
لا أستطيع سماع ما يقولونه بوضوح.
I want to use your connection with Commander Xu to pull some strings.
أريد استخدام اتصالك مع القائد Xu لسحب بعض الخيوط.
Of course.
بالطبع.
You'll definitely get your fair share of benefits.
سوف تحصل بالتأكيد على نصيبك العادل من الفوائد.
Sir.
سيد.
You...
أنت...
Alright.
على ما يرام.
What does that hand gesture mean?
ماذا تعني هذه الإشارة باليد؟
It seems like
يبدو مثل
they're making some kind of deal.
إنهم يعقدون صفقة ما.
Okay.
تمام.
Come on.
تعال.
Let's drink.
دعونا نشرب.
Why has she been
لماذا كانت
eating so much lately?
هل تأكل كثيرًا في الآونة الأخيرة؟
Has she been doing physical labor?
هل كانت تقوم بأعمال بدنية؟
They might know what happened back then.
ربما يعرفون ما حدث في ذلك الوقت.
Father,
أب،
I miss you so much.
أفتقدك كثيرًا.
Sir, may I ask you something?
سيدي هل يجوز لي أن أسألك شيئا؟
Come.
يأتي.
It's you again.
أنت مرة أخرى.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Why are you wandering around in the kitchen?
لماذا تتجول في المطبخ؟
I just wanted to take a look.
أردت فقط أن ألقي نظرة.
The kitchen is a restricted area.
المطبخ هو منطقة محظورة.
Front hall workers are not allowed in here.
لا يُسمح للعاملين في القاعة الأمامية بالدخول إلى هنا.
This has always been the rule at Fulu Restaurant.
لقد كانت هذه هي القاعدة دائمًا في مطعم فولو.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
a busboy like you
عامل نظافة مثلك
could contaminate the kitchen and make customers sick.
يمكن أن يؤدي ذلك إلى تلويث المطبخ وإصابة العملاء بالمرض.
Even your life wouldn't be enough compensation.
حتى حياتك لن تكون تعويضًا كافيًا.
But I haven't done anything.
ولكنني لم أفعل شيئا.
That doesn't matter.
هذا لا يهم.
I must give you a few lashes today to teach you a lesson.
يجب أن أعطيك بعض الجلدات اليوم لتعليمك درسًا.
Hey, innkeeper!
مهلا، صاحب النزل!
If you want to hit someone, hit me.
إذا كنت تريد ضرب شخص ما، اضربني.
Don't hit my sister.
لا تضرب أختي
If she's hurt, she won't be able to work.
إذا أصيبت، فلن تكون قادرة على العمل.
Look at that, she's got an old flame speaking up for her.
أنظر إلى هذا، هناك حبيب قديم يتحدث نيابة عنها.
I can see you're not really here to work.
أستطيع أن أرى أنك لست هنا للعمل حقًا.
Flirting with everyone.
مغازلة الجميع.
Either you're flirting with the waiters or wandering aimlessly in the kitchen.
إما أنك تغازل النوادل أو تتجول بلا هدف في المطبخ.
I won't hit you today.
لن أضربك اليوم
Who knows what trouble you'll cause me later.
من يعلم ما هي المشاكل التي ستسببها لي لاحقًا.
She usually...
إنها عادة...
If you're going to hit, then hit.
إذا كنت تريد أن تضرب، فاضرب.
Stop wasting your breath.
توقف عن إهدار أنفاسك.
Little brat.
طفل صغير.
Who hit you?
من ضربك؟
No one.
لا احد.
Nobody hit me.
لم يضربني أحد.
Then stay at home tomorrow.
ثم ابقى في المنزل غدا.
Don't go anywhere.
لا تذهب إلى أي مكان.
Why should I?
لماذا يجب علي ذلك؟
Because I'm the eldest son of the Liu family.
لأنني الابن الأكبر لعائلة ليو.
And you are my wife.
وأنت زوجتي.
Yu.
يو.
Lei Wenli Bin.
لي وينلي بن.
Lei Pengchao.
لي بنغشاو.
Ran Pingxiang Shidi Tao Lei Wenli Bin Ping Caichao Lei Pengchao Chang Ting Yuebo Zhang Feng Chaonan Qin Dongzhu Qundong Liu Jinghong Jun.
Ran Pingxiang Shidi Tao Lei Wenli Bin Ping Caichao Lei Pengchao Chang Ting Yuebo Zhang Feng Chaonan Qin Dongzhu Qundong Liu Jinghong Jun.
Chao Lei Pengchao Chang Ting Yuebo Zhang Feng Chaonan Qin Dongzhu Qundong Liu Jinghong Jun Lu Ling Tuangang.
تشاو لي بينجشاو تشانغ تينغ يوبو تشانغ فنغ تشاونان تشين دونغتشو كوندونغ ليو جينغ هونغ جون لو لينغ توانغانغ.
Bo Zhang Feng Chaonan Qin Dongzhu Qundong Liu Jinghong Jun Lu Ling Tuangang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weishuo Heng.
Bo Zhang Feng Chaonan Qin Dongzhu Qundong Liu Jinghong Jun Lu Ling Tuangang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weishuo Heng.
Zhang Feng Chaonan Qin Dongzhu Qundong Liu Jinghong Jun Lu Ling Tuangang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weishuo Heng Wei.
Zhang Feng Chaonan Qin Dongzhu Qundong Liu Jinghong Jun Lu Ling Tuangang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weishuo Heng Wei.
Nan Qin Dongzhu Qundong Liu Jinghong Jun Lu Ling Tuangang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weishuo Heng Xian Gang Feng Xia.
Nan Qin Dongzhu Qundong Liu Jinghong Jun Lu Ling Tuangang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weishuo Heng Xian Gang Feng Xia.
Gang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai.
عصابة هونغ دونغبين أنت بينغانغ تشيو ليانغجون تشيان فا شان كاي.
Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa.
Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa.
Dong Liu Jinghong Jun Lu Ling Tuangang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Zhu.
Dong Liu Jinghong Jun Lu Ling Tuangang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weiishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Zhu.
Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuangang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Le.
Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuangang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weiishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Le.
Tuan Gang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun.
Tuan Gang Hong Dongbin You Pinggang Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weiishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun.
Qiu Weishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan.
Qiu Weiishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan.
Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei.
Qiu Liangjun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weiishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei.
Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong.
Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Weiishuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong.
Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Tian Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan Han Rui Long Tuo Bo Nan Fan Mo Ge.
Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Tian Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan Han Rui Long Tuo Bo Nan Fan Mo Ge.
Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Tuo Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Jie Han Rui Long Tuo Bo Nan Fan Mo Hao Kun.
لونغ وان لين شنغ منغ شين لو لونغ جانج تشون ني تيان ينغ جينغ لونغ شيويه جينغ توه فاي تشاو هوي دونغ لو جي هان روي لونغ تو بو نان فان مو هاو كون.
Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan Han Rui Long Tuo Bo Nan Fan Quan Hao Kun.
Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan Han Rui Long Tuo Bo Nan Fan Quan Hao Kun.